



GIAMPAOLO NICO LO CASCIO



Profile

Full Stack Web Developer expierienced 1 year, deployed several projects and consolidated personal skills. Highly organized, self-motivated and passionate gamer. Constantly in search of new knwoledge and open to suggestions and new challenges.

Contacts

- +49 (0) 177 576 3426
- giampaololocascio@gmail.com
- Friedrich-Ebert-Straße 12 40210 Düsseldorf

Languages

Italian ********* English

Work Experience

Internship - Fullstack Web Developer

03/2021 - Today

Neostarter Gmbh, Mönchengladbach

- · Developing new features for the Platform.
- Using modern technologies like Next.js and GraphQl Apollo.

Teacher Assistant

09/2020 - 03/2021

DCI - Digital Carreer Institute gGmbh, Düsseldorf

- Supporting the teacher's lecture providing info-material, technical support during remote classes and presentations.
- Mentored and motivated the attendands of the lecture by providing individual support and guiding them during the course of the studies.

Education

Fullstack Web Development

03/2020 - 03/2021

DCI - Digital Carreer Institute gGmbh, Düsseldorf

- 1 Year full intensive course that covered frontend and backend areas in the branch of web development.
- Attended different webinars and developed different projects and a final MERN project for the graduation.
- German course B1 level and the consolitated language skill.

B.A. Linguistic and Intercultural Mediation

10/2016 - 10/2017

University of Catania, Catania (IT) - not gratuated

- 2 Exams accomplished in Phonetics and History.
- Basic language knwoledge in German, English and Japanese.
- Phonetic and Structure of the iitalian language.

SKILLS



German

















BackEnd



Hobbys









Software







FrontEnd















